Pietro Belluschi Papers
Pietro Belluschi Papers
- Architectural projects, numbered
  - 1064 Longview Daily News, Longview, WA [Commercial], 1948
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 175)
    - Correspondence, certificates (Box 175)
    - Drawings (Tube 431)
    - Drawings (Tube 441)
    - Shop drawings (Box 418)
    - Specifications (Box 448)
  - 1065 Dr. and Mrs. Merle W. Moore Residence, Portland, OR [Residential], 1947-1949; demolished, probably late 1996
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 175)
    - Drawings (Tube 553)
    - Shop drawings (Box 418)
  - 1066 Great Northern Railroad [Other]
    - Correspondence (Box 175)
  - 1067 Firestone Equipment Co., L. A. Courtemanche, Los Angeles, CA [Commercial], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
    - Drawings (Tube 442)
  - 1068 Central Lutheran Church Parsonage, Eugene, OR [Religious], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
    - Drawings (Tube 562)
    - Specifications (Box 448)
  - 1069 Oregon State College, Home Management House, Corvallis, OR [Educational], 1047
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
    - Drawings (Tube 442)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 4 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Shop drawings (Box 418)
    - Specifications (Box 448)
  - 1070 Borg-Warner-Johnson Prefabricated Housing Project [Exhibition]
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
    - Drawings (Tube 436)
  - 1071 Pacific Telephone & Telegraph, Eugene Office Addition, Eugene, OR [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
    - Drawings (Tube 436)
    - [unidentified item]
    - Shop drawings (Box 418)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 419)
    - Specifications (Box 448)
  - 1072 Reed College Electrical Service [Industrial]
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
  - 1073 Blitz Weinhard Company Alterations [Commercial], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
    - Drawings (Tube 443)
    - Photographs (Box 438)
    - Photographs (Box 439)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 6 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Shop drawings (Box 419)
    - Specifications (Box 448)
  - 1074 William Brewster, Jr. House [Residential], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
    - Drawings (Tube 442)
  - 1075 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
  - 1076 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
  - 1077 U. S. Bank, Milwaukie-Powell Branch, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
    - Drawings, 1 sheet (Tube 444)
  - 1078 Belluschi House, Dunthoyne [Residential], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
    - Drawings (Tube 444)
    - Photographs, includes floor plan; 4 folders (Box 439)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 3)
  - 1080 Olds, Wortman and King 2d Floor Ladies Restroom [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 176)
  - 1081 Idaho Statesman, Boise, NY, ID [Commercial], 1947
    - Correspondence, 8 folders (Box 177)
    - Drawings (Tube 445)
    - Drawings (Tube 446)
    - Photographs (Box 439)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 4 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 420)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 421)
    - Specifications (Box 449)
  - 1082 Paul Wallace Display Alterations, Salem, OR [Exhibition], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 177)
    - Drawings, 2 sheets (Tube 444)
  - 1083 Benson Hotel Sidewalk Alterations, Portland, OR [Residential], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 177)
    - Drawings (Tube 443)
  - 1084 Miller Drug Store, Equitable Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 177)
  - 1086 Spellman Shoe Store / Roblee Store, Equitable Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 178)
    - Drawings (Tube 444)
  - 1087 St. Philip Neri Church, Portland, OR [Religious], 1948
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 178)
    - Drawings and renderings (Tube 564)
    - Drawings and renderings (Tube 565)
    - Photographs, includes transparencies (Box 439)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 19 items (Drawer 9 / 1; 9 / 2)
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
    - Specifications (Box 449)
  - 1088 Northwestern Bank, American Bank Building Alteration, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 178)
    - Drawings, 1 sheet (Tube 444)
  - 1089 Portland Art Museum Meeting Hall Alterations [Museum]
    - Correspondence (Box 178)
  - 1090 Zion Lutheran Church, Portland, OR [Religious], 1949
    - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 178)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 15)
    - Drawings and renderings (Tube 554)
    - Photographs (Box 439)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 8 items (Drawer 9 / 1; 9 / 2)
  - 1091 Commonwealth Space, Equitable Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 178)
  - 1092 Cigar Stand, Equitable Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 178)
  - 1093 Hurley's Store, Equitable Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 179)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 14)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - 1094 Waverly Country Club Alterations, Portland, OR [Institutional], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 179)
    - Drawings (Tube 447)
    - Photographs (Box 439)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 6 items (Drawer 9 / 5)
  - 1095 Corbett Estate, Hotel Garage Alterations, Portland, OR [Residential], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 179)
    - Drawings (Tube 450)
  - 1096 Automotive Equip. Co. Additions, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 179)
    - Drawings (Tube 450)
  - 1097 Sun Valley Development Service Station [Commercial], 1948
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 179)
    - Drawings (Tube 449)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 422)
    - Specifications (Box 449)
  - 1098 Phil Grossmayer Offices, Equitable Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 179)
    - Drawings (Tube 437)
  - 1099 Eugene Hotel Addition, Eugene, OR [Residential], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 179)
    - Drawings (Tube 450)
    - Shop drawings (Box 422)
    - Specifications (Box 449)
  - 1100 Oak St. Building
    - Correspondence, 8 folders (Box 180)
    - Correspondence, laboratory reports (Box 181)
    - Correspondence, photographs (Box 181)
    - Correspondence, progress reports (Box 181)
    - Shop drawings (Box 422)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 423)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 424)
    - Shop drawings, 4 folders (Box 425)
    - Specifications (Box 450)
  - 1101 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
  - 1102 Multnomah Bank, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
    - Drawings (Tube 448)
    - Photographs (Box 439)
    - Shop drawings (Box 426)
    - Specifications (Box 450)
  - 1103 Dr. Slocum Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
    - Drawings (Tube 447)
  - 1104 J. L. Hudson and Associates Housing project, Richland, WA [Residential], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
    - Drawings (Tube 451)
  - 1105 U. S. Bank. Sandy Blvd. Branch, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
    - Drawings (Tube 481)
  - 1106 West Coast Pattern Works, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
    - Drawings (Tube 481)
    - Specifications (Box 450)
  - 1107 Dantone Industrial Plant, Dant & Russell, Portland, OR [Industrial], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
    - Drawings (Tube 451)
  - 1108 Philip A. Joss House [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
  - 1109 Cromwell Tailors, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
    - Drawings (Tube 481)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 1)
    - Photographs (Box 439)
  - 1110 Harry Hawkins Store, Hawkins-Roberts Building, Salem, OR [Commercial], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
    - Drawings (Tube 451)
    - Shop drawings (Box 426)
    - Specifications (Box 450)
  - 1111 [John] Blodgett Jr. Residence, Santa Barbara, CA [Residential], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
    - Drawings (Tube 537)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 2)
  - 1112 Central Lutheran Church Parish House, Eugene, OR [Religious], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
    - Drawings (Tube 563)
    - Shop drawings (Box 426)
    - Specifications (Box 450)
  - 1113 Olds and King, Portland, OR [Other], 1948
    - Correspondence, basement toilet (Box 182)
    - Drawings, sidewalk alterations (Tube 453)
  - 1114 Portland Federal Savings and Loan Alterations, Vancouver, WA [Commercial], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
    - Drawings (Tube 452)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 426)
    - Specifications (Box 450)
  - 1115 Library Associaton of Portland, Portland, OR [Library]
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
  - 1116 Dant & Russell, Seventh Floor Equitable Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
    - Drawings (Tube 481)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 2 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - 1117 Benson Hotel Alterations to Basements and Toilet Rooms [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
    - Drawings
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
  - 1118 Collins Pine Co. Recreation Building [Commercial], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
    - Drawings (Tube 452)
  - 1119 Red Cross Headquarters Alterations Blood Bank [Institutional]
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 14)
    - Shop drawings (Box 426)
  - 1120 Dean and Mary L. Vincent Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
    - Drawings
    - Photographs, includes negatives (Box 439)
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
  - 1121 Marion Hotel Alterations, Salem, OR [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
    - Drawings
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
  - 1122 Reed College Memorial Plaque [Monument]
    - Correspondence (Box 182)
  - 1123 U. S. Bank, Union Ave. Branch, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 183)
    - Drawings (Tube 464)
    - Shop drawings (Box 427)
  - 1124 First Presbyterian Church, Cottage Grove, OR [Religious], 1951
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 183)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 15)
    - Drawings (Tube 559)
    - Drawings (Tube 560)
    - Photographs, 3 items (Drawer 8 / 1)
    - Photographs, nave and chancel; 1 item (Drawer 8 / 1)
    - Shop drawings, partly crossed out, with illegible handwritten note, something about "hanging file"? (Box 427)
    - Specifications (Box 450)
  - 1125 Marion County Courthouse, Salem, OR [Government], 1951
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 183)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:3)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 8)
    - Drawings (Tube 545)
    - Drawings (Tube 546)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 20 items (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1126 Oregon Liquor Control Commission Addition, Portland, OR [Government], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 456)
  - 1127 Sherman Clay Co. Elevators [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1128 Holy Redeemer Parish School Building, Oakland, CA [Educational], 1946
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 456)
  - 1129 Lumbermen's Building Alteration [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings
    - Shop drawings, entrance (Oversize 2)
  - 1130 Clearwater Plumbing [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:3)
  - 1131 Huntington-Malarky / Hunt Malarkey Residence, Sun Valley, ID [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:3)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1132 Spring Street Apartments Project, Portland, OR [Residential], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 455)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 3)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1133 Marion Hotel Tavern [Other]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
  - 1134 Belluschi Farmhouse Alts, Portland, OR [Residential], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 480)
    - Photographs, includes magazine clipping; 2 folders (Box 439)
  - 1136 David Eyre House [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
  - 1137 Holy Redeemer Parish Convent, Portland, OR [Religious], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 480)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1138 Drummond-Storey Dog and Cat Hospital, Portland, OR [Hospital], 1948
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 479)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1139 Wilbur Methodist Church, Portland, OR [Religious], 1948
    - Correspondence, centenary (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 480)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, job title given as "Centenary Wilbur Methodist Church"; 1 item (Drawer 9 / 1; 9 / 2)
  - 1140 Mathis Apartment House Project [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
  - 1142 H. G. Pressler / Ressler House, Oak Grove, OR [Residential], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 479)
  - 1144 Liberty St. Building, Salem, OR [Other], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings, 1 sheet (Tube 479)
  - 1145 Dr. John Raaf Clinic Building, Portland, OR [Hospital], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 479)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 2 items (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
  - 1146 Library Associaton Art Room Alterations, Portland, OR [Library]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1147 Pacific Telephone & Telegraph Transformer Vault [Industrial]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
  - 1149 Florence Distribution Co. Office / Menduni Warehouse and Sales Building [Commercial], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 480)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 2 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - 1150 Pacific Telephone & Telegraph, Baker Office, Baker, OR [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:3)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1151 Olds, Wortman and King, elevators for warehouse [Industrial]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
    - Shop drawings (Box 427)
  - 1152 Olds, Wortman and King, entrance [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 184)
  - 1153 Pacific Telephone & Telegraph, Springfield Office, Springfield, OR [Commercial], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Drawings (Tube 478)
    - Shop drawings (Box 427)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1154 Courtemanche Residence Alterations, McMinnville, OR [Residential], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Drawings (Tube 478)
  - 1155 Robinson Miles (or Miles Robinson) Residence, Walla Walla, WA [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Drawings (Tube 478)
  - 1156 Sacred Heart Church, Oswego, OR [Religious]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 3 items (Drawer 9 / 1; 9 / 2)
  - 1157 U.S. National Bank, Burglar Proof Partition - 1 sheet, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Drawings (Tube 478)
  - 1158 Merle Moore Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Photographs, may also pertain to Job #1065; 3 folders (Box 440)
  - 1159 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
  - 1160 House at Linwood Heights, Chamber of Commerce, Vancouver, WA [Residential], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Drawings (Tube 478)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1161 Linfield College Expansion Program [Educational]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
  - 1162 Bank of California Alterations [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
  - 1163 Electrical Distributing Co., Portland, OR [Commercial], 1949
    - Correspondence, underpinning (Box 185)
    - Drawings, 1 sheet (Tube 477)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 1)
  - 1164 American Red Cross Headquarters Alterations, Portland, OR [Institutional], 1949
    - Drawings, 3 sheets (Tube 477)
  - 1165 Alterations For John Mulkey
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:3)
  - 1167 Housing project at Cedar Hills, Cedar Hills, OR [Residential], 1949; duplexes
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Drawings (Tube 477)
    - Specifications (Box 451)
  - 1168 Cedar Hills Solar House [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1169 Dean Witter, Equitable Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
  - 1170 Lynridge House at Cedar Hills, Cedar Hills, OR [Residential], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Drawings (Tube 477)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1171 Wilson Residence, Portland, OR [Residential], 1949
    - Drawings, 2 sheets (Tube 477)
  - 1172 Catlin School Dormitories, Portland, OR [Educational], 1949
    - Drawings (Tube 477)
  - 1173 A. M. Work Residence, Seaside, OR [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
    - Drawings (Tube 477)
  - 1174 Arlington Heights Grocery [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 185)
  - 1175 Corvallis Telephone & Telegraph Company, Corvallis, OR [Commercial], 1950
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 186)
    - Drawings (Tube 476)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 427)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1176 Pacific Telephone & Telegraph, Oak Grove, Milwaukie and Oswego [Commercial], 1950
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 186)
    - Drawings (Tube 474)
    - Shop drawings (Box 428)
    - Specifications, job 1176-A (Box 452)
    - Specifications, job 1176-B (Box 452)
  - 1177 U. S. Bank, Citizens Branch, Alterations, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 186)
    - Drawings (Tube 475)
    - Shop drawings (Box 428)
  - 1178 Standard Insurance Co. Alterations [Commercial], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 186)
    - Drawings, 1 sheet (Tube 477)
  - 1179 Dr. Campbell Clinic, Salem, OR [Hospital], 1949
    - Correspondence (Box 186)
    - Drawings (Tube 477)
  - 1180 L. A. Courtemanche Warehouse and Display Building, McMinnville, OR [Residential], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 187)
    - Drawings (Tube 475)
    - Shop drawings (Box 428)
  - 1181 Dr. Campbell House Alterations, Salem, OR [Residential], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 187)
    - Drawings (Tube 475)
  - 1183 Penthouse, Equitable Building
    - Correspondence (Box 187)
    - Photographs, job 1183-A; exterior and interior; includes negatives and transparencies; 5 folders (Box 440)
    - Photographs, job 1183-A; exterior and interior (Oversize 5)
    - Photographs, job 1183-B; construction; 2 folders (Box 440)
    - Photographs, job 1183-C (Box 532)
  - 1184 Nordstrom's Shoe Store Part 2, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1950
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 187)
    - Drawings (Tube 472)
    - Drawings (Tube 473)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 428)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 429)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1185 Ft. Richardson, Enlisted Men's Service Club, Ft. Richardson, AK [Government], 1950
    - Correspondence, cost records; 2 folders (Box 187)
    - Drawings (Tube 474)
    - Shop drawings, design and analysis, electrical and mechanical work (Box 429)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1186 Ft. Richardson, Enlisted Men's Barracks, 500-man, Ft. Richardson, AK [Government], 1950
    - Correspondence, job title given as "U.S. Army, England"; 3 folders (Box 187)
    - Shop drawings, design and analysis, electrical and mechanical work (Box 429)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
    - Tracings and prints
  - 1187 Ft. Richardson, Enlisted Men's Barracks, 200-man, Ft. Richardson, AK [Government], 1950
    - Drawings (Tube 471)
    - Shop drawings, design and analysis, electrical and mechanical work (Box 429)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1188 Charleston Shopping Center, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1950
    - Drawings (Tube 470)
  - 1189 Linfield College Athletic Center, McMinnville, OR [Educational], 1950
    - Drawings (Tube 470)
  - 1190 St. Thomas More, Grade School and Rectory Addition, Gymnasium [?], Portland, OR [Educational], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Drawings (Tube 504)
    - Shop drawings (Box 429)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1191 Enlisted Men's Barracks, 750-man, Alaska [Government]
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Drawings (Tube 468)
    - Shop drawings (Box 430)
  - 1192 U.S. Bank, Union Ave. Branch, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Drawings (Tube 470)
    - Shop drawings (Box 430)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1193 Physicians Building Addition, Salem, OR [Commercial], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Drawings (Tube 470)
    - Photographs (Box 532)
  - 1194 H. Hawk Autopark at High and Ferry, Salem, OR [Other], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Drawings (Tube 467)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1195 Lane Investment Company Alterations [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - 1196 Payless Drugstore [Commercial], 1950
    - Correspondence, job location given as Salem (Box 188)
    - Drawings, job location given as Portland (Tube 470)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - 1197 E. H. Johnson House, Orenko, OR [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Drawings (Tube 469)
    - Specifications (Box 452)
  - 1198 Autopark and Service Station at Ferris, Salem, OR [Other], 1950
    - Correspondence, job title given as "Marion Car Park, Ferry and Commercial St." (Box 188)
    - Drawings (Tube 469)
    - Shop drawings, job title given as "Garage, Miami" (Box 430)
    - Specifications (Box 453)
  - 1199 Meier and Frank Multipurpose Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Photographs, includes picture of a drawing; could also be Job 40 (Box 532)
  - 1200 Developments of two city blocks, Portland OR [Urban Planning]
    - Drawings (Tube 467)
  - 1201 Wallace [Walls?] Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 13)
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
    - Specifications (Box 453)
  - 1202 Mountain House for J. D. Kroeker, Oak Grove, OR [Residential], 1949-1950
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
  - 1203 A. G. Griffith Residence, Oswego, OR [Residential], 1950-1951
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 13)
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
  - 1204 Enlisted Men's Barracks, Alaska [Government]
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
  - 1205 U. S. Air Force, Larson Field [Government]
    - Correspondence (Box 188)
  - 1206 U. S. Army, McChord Field [Government]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
    - Specifications (Box 453)
  - 1207 U. S. Army, Portland Base [Government]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
  - 1208 American Bank Building Alterations, Portland, OR [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
  - 1210 John Platt House Addt'n. [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
  - 1211 U. S. Bank, Safe Deposit and Storage Vaults [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
  - 1212 Johnson shop, Salem, OR [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 13)
    - Photographs, 3 items (Drawer 8 / 1)
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
    - Specifications (Box 453)
  - 1213 [unknown; possibly Reed College entrance pylon]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
  - 1214 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
  - 1215 Pacific Telephone & Telegraph, Cypress office, Cypress, OR [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Specifications (Box 453)
  - 1216 Zoods Port Angeles Store Alterations, Port Angeles, WA [Commercial], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
    - Drawings (Tube 467)
  - 1218 Oregonian Building Alterations [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
  - 1220 Fort Richardson, Field House, Alaska [Government]
    - Correspondence (Box 189)
    - Correspondence, job 1220-1 (Box 190)
    - Shop drawings, job title given as "Ladd Air Force Base, Service Club" (Box 430)
    - Specifications (Box 453)
  - 1221 Alaska Air Force Bases [Government]
    - Shop drawings, Eielson Air Force Base, Field House (Box 430)
    - Shop drawings, Fort Richardson, Indoor Training Facility (Box 430)
    - Specifications (Box 453)